Welcome everyone to web API's and asynchronous applications.
欢迎各位来学习 Web API 和异步应用课程
It's what we're all here for.
这是我们来到这里的目的
My name is Daniel, and I'm going to lead you
我是 Daniel 我将带领大家
through the process of learning how to develop
学习如何使用 Web API 开发
an asynchronous JavaScript web app that uses
异步 JavaScript Web 应用
an external web API and dynamically updates the U-I of your web app.
并且动态更新 Web 界面
Now, before we dive into the exciting details,
在深入令人兴奋的细节之前
let me introduce myself a bit.
先允许我简单介绍一下自己
So you have some idea of who it is that's trying to teach you all this JavaScript.
好让各位知道在这儿教 JavaScript 的家伙是谁
My name is Daniel.
我叫 Daniel
For the first half of my professional life,
职业生涯的前半部分
I directed an arts-based Public Health Program for young people in Brooklyn, New York.
我在纽约布鲁克林 管理着一个以艺术为基础 面向年轻人的公共健康项目
I was also a storyteller and a performance poet,
我是一个说书人 一个表演诗人
including being a national poetry slam champion and an artist and residence at UC,
曾经赢得过全国诗歌朗诵赛冠军 我还是加州大学圣芭芭拉分校的
Santa Barbara, where I taught a class titled,
特邀艺术家 在该校英语系 我教授一门
The Poetics of Struggle in the English Department.
叫做  "奋斗诗学" 的课程
Now, stemming from my work with youth and my poetry,
由于和年轻人一起工作还有写诗的缘故
I became fascinated with the ability that technology
我热衷于使用科技
presented to communicate big ideas and be harnessed for social good.
交流创意 服务社会
I received my Master's degree in Interactive Telecommunications at
我在纽约大学获得了互动传播专业的硕士学位
NYU and began synthesizing my creative background with the technical skills of coding.
并开始将我的创意背景与编程技术相结合
Since earning my Master's degree,
拿到硕士学位后
I've done Digital Design and Development as
我一直在纽约 为 VidCode 和 Codecademy 的
an employee at vid code and code Academy in New York.
交互式课程
Working on interactive curriculum topics
进行数字设计和开发工作
ranging from test-driven development with JavaScript,
从使用 JavaScript 的测试驱动开发
to data visualizations with Python.
到用 Python 实现数据可视化
That brings us to here,
接下来 我们一起学习
the topic of Web API's and Asynchronous Applications.
Web API 和异步应用程序
Let's take a quick overview tour of the path will go through on this learning process.
我们先快速浏览一遍学习路线
This course will begin by teaching you how to set up
这门课将从教你如何安装
a Node and Express development environment,
Node 和 Express 开发环境开始
which is the essential combo for making many a web application.
这是许多 Web 应用都要用到的技术组合
Understanding how to use even the basic functions of Node and Express,
学会如何使用 Node 和 Express 的基本功能以后
will unlock a whole world of development possibilities.
我们将打开 Web 开发世界的大门 00:01:51,155 --&gt; 00:01:53,855 也许你已经听过 Node 或 Express
Maybe you've tried it on your own already and feel confused or
也许你已经用过它们 但感到困惑 甚至倍感挫折
frustrated or maybe you've had some development success with Node and Express.
或者你已经用 Node 和 Express 成功地开发出一些应用
No matter where you're coming from,
但不管你来自哪里 水平如何
I promise you will learn some fundamental knowledge about how web development works,
你都会在这里学到如何使用 Node 和 Express
starting from the Node and Express lessons.
开发 Web 应用的基础知识